The Amanda Steele Show today goes to the super sheroes in real life.
All right, so these Atlanta residents have expressed concern over the increasing number of cars being booted by private companies.
So two good citizens have taken matters into their own hands.
Check them out.
The boot girls in Buckhead are two best friends with a key that unlocks metal boots and they're making hundreds of dollars using it.
We don't got no beef with the people that put boots on the cars, but we're going to take it off.
We're going to take it off.
I love this because when the establishment oppresses its people, the people will rise.
I pray for their continued success and prosperity.
And I hope they get a movie deal, a comic book, a Saturday morning cartoon, a cereal, all the things.
Today's lockdown goes to a butt naked boat.
Y'all, there's a nude cruise.
Oh, wow.
It's called the Big Nude Boat.
It'll depart from Miami for an 11-day trip around the Caribbean, accommodating up to 2,300 passengers.
The only time you'll be required to wear any clothes is in the dining rooms.
But the outside buffet is all nude.
Wow.
Oh, I don't know.
No, thank you.
I'm all for, you know, embracing body positivity, but I just, I don't want to, it's just, there's too many juices.
I mean, it does figure that it would depart from Miami because Floridians are used to seeing a prick in public, but they call it a governor.
Ba-dum-bum.
We are.